Anton Vakhrushin

Senior Frontend Developer

As a skilled frontend developer with 5+ years of experience, I have delivered top-performing products that have been widely embraced by over a million users worldwide. My leadership and management skills have enabled me to manage development teams, design business systems, and ensure exceptional product quality. As the most experienced frontend developer at my current organization, I autonomously determine the technical direction of projects and provide valuable guidance to other developers.

Work Experience

Lead Web Developer

Symplast 🗹

#1 mobile EHR & Practice Management solution for the medical aesthetics industry in the USA

6mos. Oct, 2022 - Present

- Successfully optimized the performance of the application by reducing the main project bundle size from 4.7 MB to 537 KB (-89%).
- Improved key performance indicators such as First Contentful Paint, Time To Interactive, Largest Contentful Paint, and Speed Index, resulting in a much faster application and enhanced user experience.
- Implemented several customer-centric features that improved payment setup between patients and insurance companies, resulting in increased customer satisfaction and retention.
- Implemented coding best practices, automated documentation generation, and developed a high-quality component library using Storybook to minimize errors and ensure top-notch code.

Senior frontend developer

Skillbox 2

EdTech Leader in Russia. Acquired by VK Group

2yrs 6mos. Sep, 2019 - Feb, 2022

- Led a 3-person team and managed the frontend of a learning management system.
- Created a comprehensive component library consisting of 42 directives and components.
- Streamlined technical and business processes, reducing critical errors per release by 50% and unfinished tasks in sprints from 23% to 5%.
- Enabled international expansion through the implementation of multilingual support.
- Built a video player with video.js for the platform's 30,000+ tutorials.

antony.vakhrushin@gmail.com

+7 985 0705 321

• Moscow, Russia

github.com/RedtigerAV

in linkedin.com/in/anton-vakhrushin

Skills

Hard skills

Javascript Typescript Angular HTML

CSS SCSS Angular CDK RxJS NgRx

NGXS Angular Material Video.js

Nrwl NX Docker Webpack Git

Sentry Storybook NodeJS Express

Rest API SOLID Jest Spectator Eslint

Prettier Swagger OpenAPI Gitlab CI

Soft skills

Team management

Work on specifications

Customer interaction

Organization of processes

Conducting an interview

Last projects

Quick Quote (May 2022)

Progressive Web Application for getting inspired and motivated by accessing 1,000,000+ quotes from great people.

www.quickquote.space

github.com/RedtigerAV/quick-quote

TimGO Jira Plugin (Jul 2020)

Atlassian Jira plugin for planning and labor accounting in Agile projects



github.com/RedtigerAV/jira-plugin

Frontend developer

Tinkoff Bank 🗹

The world's largest digital bank. Best Digital Bank Award 2020. *lyrs 8mos, Jan, 2018 - Aug, 2019*

- Built a personal bank account for business, utilized by over 600k users.
- Designed and developed Frame Manager an all-in-one super-app, integrating 20+ distinct products.
- Engineered a secure and efficient SSO user authentication system.

Education

2016 - 2020, Moscow, Russia

Bachelor of Computer Science in National Research University «Higher School of Economics»

Languages

English: Full Professional Proficiency

Russian: Native